question_data = {
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "History",
         "question": "United States President John F. Kennedy was assassinated during his presidential "
                     "\nmotorcade in Atlanta, Georgia on November 22nd, 1963.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "History",
         "question": "Adolf Hitler was a german soldier in World War I.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "History",
         "question": "Thomas Crapper was a plumber who invented the "
                     "flushing toilet.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "History",
         "question": "The French Kingdom helped the United States gain their independence over Great Britain "
                     "\nduring the Revolutionary War.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "History",
         "question": "The United States Department of Homeland Security was formed in response to the "
                     "\nSeptember 11th attacks.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "History",
         "question": "Former United States Presidents John Adams and Thomas Jefferson died within hours of "
                     "\neach other.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "History",
         "question": "In World War ll, Great Britain used inflatable tanks on the ports of Great Britain to "
                     "\ndivert Hitler away from Normandy D-day landing.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "History",
         "question": "The United States of America declared their independence from the British Empire on "
                     "\nJuly 4th, 1776.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "History",
         "question": "The United States was a member of the League of Nations.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "History",
         "question": "The Tienanmen Square protests of 1989 were held in "
                     "\nHong Kong.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]}
